Is it ok if I come in?
我可以进来吗?
Yes.
Hi. The indisputable fact is that you are sixteen.
Hi. 你现在是16岁,这个事实不容置疑.
We're going to have to work out when you're already sixteen.
我们必须搞清楚你什么时候已经16岁了,
And you're already sixteen.
什么时候才刚刚16岁.
According to you I'm going to be "only" sixteen until I'm ninety.
照你的说法,等我90岁的时候, 也不过才“刚刚”16岁.
You're right,
你说得对.
I will be worrying about you longer than you want to know.
我为你操心的时间肯定比你想知道的要长.
But I don't want you to worry.
可我并不要你操心.
It's not my fault if you do.
如果你非要为我操心的话这不能怪我.
Well, some situations worry us more than others, Beth.
Well, 有些情况会比其他情况更令我们担心, Beth.
This trip is one.
这次旅行就是其中之一.
I'm sorry it's such a disappointment to you.
如果这令你失望的话,我很抱歉.
I really am.
真的很抱歉.
You're just saying that to be nice, Daddy.
你那样说只是想示好, Daddy.
When are you going to let me grow up?
你打算什么时候才让我长大?
Believe me, honey,
相信我, 亲爱的,
soon you'll be doing things you never thought possible.
不久以后你就会做你以前觉得不可能做的事情.
-Say the trip were in two years... -Two years!
-比如说,两年以后再 参加旅行... -两年！
I can't do anything for two years...
那这两年我什么也不能干...
Listen, listen. You'd be eighteen.
你听我说, 听我说, 那时你就18岁了,
You'd be better prepared.
准备就更充分了,
There'd be no question about the trip.
出门旅行就不会有问题了.
So I can do it in two years?
那我两年以后肯定能去吗?
Do you promise?
你保证?
Oh boy. You've been doing this since you were a minute old.
Oh boy. 你出生一分钟之的时候就这样了.
What?
怎样了?
Wrapping me around your little finger.
把我绕在你的小手指上任你摆布呀.
Do you promise?
你保证吗?